copyhackers.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Copywriting by Copy Hackers

Last updated November 11, 2011

**EASY-TO-READ SUMMARY**

CopyHackers.com and Joanna Wiebe will make every reasonable effort to protect your privacy when you’re using our site. We ask that you do your best to help us help you by keeping your account secure.

Copy Hackers operates several websites including http://www.copyhackers.com. It is COPY HACKERS’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, COPY HACKERS collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. COPY HACKERS’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how COPY HACKERS’s visitors use its website. From time to time, COPY HACKERS may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

COPY HACKERS also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our sites. COPY HACKERS only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to COPY HACKERS’s websites choose to interact with COPY HACKERS in ways that require COPY HACKERS to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that COPY HACKERS gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with COPY HACKERS are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, COPY HACKERS collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with COPY HACKERS. COPY HACKERS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
COPY HACKERS may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, COPY HACKERS may monitor contributions to our site(s). COPY HACKERS may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, COPY HACKERS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
COPY HACKERS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on COPY HACKERS’s behalf or to provide services available at COPY HACKERS’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using COPY HACKERS’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. COPY HACKERS will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, COPY HACKERS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when COPY HACKERS believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of COPY HACKERS, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a COPY HACKERS website and have supplied your email address, COPY HACKERS may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with COPY HACKERS and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. COPY HACKERS takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. COPY HACKERS uses cookies to help COPY HACKERS identify and track visitors, their usage of COPY HACKERS website, and their website access preferences. COPY HACKERS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using COPY HACKERS’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of COPY HACKERS’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by COPY HACKERS and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, COPY HACKERS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in COPY HACKERS’s sole discretion. COPY HACKERS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Our appreciation to Automattic Inc. for making their privacy policy available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license. We have used their privacy policy as the basis for ours. Read more here: http://automattic.com/privacy/

_Loading..._

Get high-converting copywriting strategies every Tuesday:

100% spam-free.
